(Raj:)Oh, Howard, stop.
(Howard:)Trust me, you're not Jewish,
that's how they get you.
(Raj:)You're being silly.
I can leave whenever I want.
(Howard:)Oh, really?
Where are your clothes and your shoes?
(Raj:)They're on the chair right over...
(Raj:)Oy vey.
Hello, homewrecker.
(Penny:)What did I do?
(Sheldon:)You gave Leonard somewhere to go.
(Sheldon:)Thanks to you, Amy's out
buying his and hers bath towels.
(Sheldon:)Like I'd ever dry myself with something
that has a possessive pronoun on it.
(Penny:)Okay, listen...
(Penny:)...the truth is
I don't want him living with me.
(Sheldon:)Great. Kick him out, break his heart,
everybody wins.
No, I don't wanna break his heart,
I love him. This is happening too fast.
(Sheldon:)You think this is fast?
It is just a matter of time before
I see Amy's leg stubble in my shower.
(Penny:)Yeah, and I've seen those legs.
You might wanna get some Drano.